NEW YORK STATE CONFERENCE OF LOCAL MENTAL HYGIENE DIRECTORS RECORDS (APAP315) 1950-2009
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Office of Legislative and Government Affairs Director, 1991-2003; Undated; 3; 3.0 cu. ft.
  - Proposed new Part 551 comments and prior arrival review issues, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Proposed revisions to Part 592- Comprehensive Outpatient Program, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Redeployment of mental health resources for the 21st century, 1997 December-1998 January (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Reinvestment- General, 1993-1995; 1997 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Reinvestment- General, 1993-1998 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Reinvestment Group (The One Bill Group), 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Reinvestment guidelines, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Reinvestment guidelines, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Reinvestment guidelines, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Reinvestment implementation, 1992-1995 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Reinvestment implementation, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Reinvestment implementation- Acts to amend state finance and mental hygiene laws, 1992 October 19; 1993 November 01; Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Reinvestment- Legislation and correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Reinvestment- letter-writing campaign, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Reinvestment- Memos of support, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Reinvestment overview, 1993; 1995 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Reinvestment resolutions, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Special Needs Plans, 1997-2000 (Box 3, Folder 13-14)
  - Special Needs Plans (information and data), 1997-1998; Undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Special Needs Plans (information and data), 1998 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Survey- Reinvestment evaluation, 1997 April (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - TAP Day, Rensselaerville Institute, September 2002, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Welfare reform- Act to amend social services law, 1996 December 02 (Box 3, Folder 19-20)
  - Welfare reform- "Putting the Pieces Together" by Senator M.L. Rath and act to amend education law, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- County Plans, Operations, and Government, 1980-2009; Undated; 4; 4.2 cu. ft.
  These records are specific to the counties of New York as they participated in coordinated care efforts for people with mental health needs. There are documents regarding activities unique to certain counties, such as closures of facilities and resignations of Conference members. There are also letters, memos, and reports covering topics like mandate relief recommendations, comprehensive outpatient programs, health needs surveys, and funding issues.
  - 135th Anniversary celebration of the Schuyler Center, 2006 November 16 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Albany County, 1992-1997 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Albany County letter to Mental Health Commissioners, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Amendment of 14NYCRR Parts 587 and 588- Comprehensive mandate relief, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Broome County, 1991; 1993-1994; 1997 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Broome County- Annual report, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Broome County- Annual report, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - By-laws and amendments, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - By-laws amendments ballots, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Cayuga County, 1991; 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Chautauqua County, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Chemung County, 1991-1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Clinton County, 1991-1994 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Columbia County, 1990; 1995 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Community of practice for local partners, 2009; Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Consolidated budget reporting manual and forms, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Cortland County, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - County plans A-F, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - County plans F-H, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - County plans J-O, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - County plans O-S, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - County plans S-W, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - County responses- Comprehensive Outpatient Program, 1991; 1995; 1997 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - County responses- Comprehensive Outpatient Program, 1991; Undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - County testimony on Office of Mental Retardation and Developmentally Disabled regulation review, 1995; Undated (Box 2, Folder 1-3)
  - Delaware County, 1990-1993 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Delaware County, 1994-1996 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Department of Mental Hygiene property utilization book, Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Dictionary of Mental Health Terms, 1989; 1998 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Directors of community service, 1989; 1994; 1997 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Dutchess County, 1991-1994; 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Erie County, 1991-1995; Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Erie County, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Essex County, 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Fingerlakes region, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Forms of county government, 1990; 1993; Undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Franklin County, 1990; 1993 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Fulton County, 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Genesee County, 1991; 1993; Undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Guidelines reinvestment plan for 1995, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Jefferson County, 1991; 1993; 1995 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Lewis County, 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Livingston County, 1992-1993; 1995 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Local area plan guidelines for 1995, 1994 April (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - "Local Government and Managed Governance", Presented at Managed Care and Managed Change Conference, 1996 June (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Local Services Plan for Alcoholism and Substance Abuse Services- County guidance, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Madison County, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Mandate relief recommendations, 1994-1995; Undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Mandate relief recommendations, 1995; Undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Mandate relief recommendations, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Manuals: "Mental Health Care in America" and "Community Health Needs Assessment in a Managed Care Environment", 1995; 2001 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Mental hygiene law, Title E, 1990; Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Mission statement, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Monroe County, 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Montgomery County, 1992-1993; 1997 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Nassau County, 1992-1994; 1996 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Nassau County, 1992-1995; Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - New York City, 1991; 1994 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - New York City, 1994-1996 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - New York City: "Deinstitutionalization- An Epilogue", 1985 December 03 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Niagara County, 1991; 1993 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - North Country directors, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - NYS Department of Mental Hygiene Consolidated Fiscal Reporting Manual (Agency administration expenses), 1988 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - NYS Department of Mental Hygiene Consolidated Fiscal Reporting Manual (DAAA program definitions and code numbers), 1988; Undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - NYS Office Alcoholism and Substance Abuse Services- County planning data supplements, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - NYS Office of Alcoholism and Substance Abuse Services- Local services plan guidelines, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - NYSCLMHD Annual Report, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - NYSCLMHD Annual Report, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - NYSCLMHD strategic framework, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Office of Mental Health-Comprehensive Outpatient Programs, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Office of Regulatory and Management Assistance Taskforce on CFR Reform final report, 1994 March (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Oneida County, 1980; 1991; 1995 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Onondaga County, 1990-1994 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Ontario County, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Orange County, 1990-1994 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Planning guidelines for counties and boroughs, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Prepaid mental health plan: Office of Mental Health, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Prepaid mental health plan: Office of Mental Health, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Prepaid mental health plan: Office of Mental Health, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Prospectivity- Comprehensive Outpatient Programs, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Putnam County, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Regulation review process by county, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Rensselaer County, 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Rensselaer County: "Addressing the needs of Incarcerated Women with Concurring Disorders: One Program's Response"- Summer 1998 Issue of Jail Suicide/Mental Health Update with accompanying letter, 1998 June; 1996 June (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Resignation letter of Lloyd Sederer, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Rockland County, 1993; 1995; Undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Saratoga County, 1993; Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Schenectady County, 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Schenectady County, 1993-1994; 1996; Undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Schoharie County, 1991; 1993 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Schuyler County, 1991-1992; 1994 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Schuyler County mental health plan, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Schuyler County mental retardation/developmental disabilities plan, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Schuyler County substance abuse plan, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Seneca County, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - St. Lawrence County, 1991-1993 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Statewide directory, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Steuben County, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Suffolk County, 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Sullivan County, 1991; 1993; 1997 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Survey on the NYS public mental health system, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Tioga County, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Tioga County, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Tioga County, 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Tioga County, 1994-1997 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Ulster County, 1991-1993; 1995 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Warren/Washington County, 1991-1992; 1995 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Wayne County, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Westchester County, 1992-1995 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Western region, Undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Western Regional county directors, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Wyoming County, 1991; 1993 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Yates County, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Projects and Committees, 1979-2001; Undated; 5; 5.0 cu. ft.
  This series focuses on some of the Conference’s more specific endeavors, including (but not limited to) those with definitive start and end dates as opposed to ongoing tasks. Examples include the Kids Oneida project, the Commission on the 21st Century, various grant applications, and the committees for developmental disabilities and chemical dependency.
  - Center for Behavioral Health Institute (CBHI), 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Chemical Dependency Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Chemical Dependency Committee: Managed care joint meeting minutes, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Chemical Dependency Committee: Meeting Minutes, 1994 October-1995 June (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Chemical Dependency Committee: Meeting Minutes, 1995 October (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Chemical Dependency Committee: Meeting Minutes, etc., 1996 December (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Chemical Dependency Committee: Member Lists, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Chemical Dependency Committee: OASAS Budget, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Chemical Dependency Committee: OASAS Regional Office Separation, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Chemical Task Force of the M.H.S.C., 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - CLMHD/OMRDD Partnership: Background and Planning materials, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - CLMHD/OMRDD Partnership: Configuration of Developmental Disabilities Services Offices, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - CLMHD/OMRDD Partnership: Interim Report, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - CLMHD/OMRDD Partnership: Meeting Minutes, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 14-16)
  - CLMHD/OMRDD Partnership: Pilot Project, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - CLMHD/OMRDD Partnership: Pilot Project committee meeting, 1996 May-1996 August (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - CLMHD/OMRDD Partnership: Pilot steering committee meeting, 1996 January (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - CLMHD/OMRDD Partnership: Pilot Steering Subgroup Meeting, 1996 February (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - CLMHD/OMRDD Partnership: Pilot Subcommittee Meeting, 1996 March (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - CLMHD/OMRDD Partnership: Planning letter and draft of "Supports and Services for People with Developmental Disabilities" report, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - CLMHD/OMRDD Partnership: Problem Solving, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - CLMHD/OMRDD Partnership: Survey of County experiences with Developmental Disabilities Services Offices-Draft, Undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - CLMHD/OMRDD Partnership: Survey of County experiences with Developmental Disabilities Services Offices-Draft, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Commission on 21st Century: "At the Crossroads" report, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Commission on 21st Century: Children's Mental Health Services Checklist, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Commission on 21st Century: Committee Recommendations, Final Report, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Commission on 21st Century: Committee Recommendations, Third Draft, Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Commission on 21st Century: Implementation Plan, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Commission on 21st Century: January Meeting, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Commission on 21st Century: Local Stewardship, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Commission on 21st Century: Meeting Advertisements, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 2-3)
  - Commission on 21st Century: Mailing lists for press, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Commission on 21st Century: Photographs, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Commission on 21st Century: Powerpoint presentation, paper and CD, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Commission on 21st Century: Press conference, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Commission on 21st Century: Public testimony, 1998 October (Box 2, Folder 8-9)
  - Commission on 21st Century: September Meeting, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Commission on 21st Century: Subcommittee work, 1996-1999 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Commission on 21st Century: Technical Assistance Collaborative, commission biographies, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Commission on 21st Century: Technical Assistance Collaborative, commission members, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Commission on 21st Century: Technical Assistance Collaborative, conference call and correspondence, 1998-1999; Undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Commission on 21st Century: Technical Assistance Collaborative, original contract, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Commission on 21st Century: Technical Assistance Collaborative, proposal, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Community service boards matrix, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Community Support Programs (CSP) "20 Questions" responses, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 18-19)
  - Community Support Programs (CSP) Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1994 (Box 2, Folder 20-21)
    Must consult archivist before viewing this material.
  - Community Support Programs (CSP) planning contest-letters and statistics [RESTRICTED], 1994 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Community Support Programs (CSP) contest responses [RESTRICTED], 1994 (Box 2, Folder 23-24)
  - Community Support Programs (CSP) planning contest cover forms [RESTRICTED], 1994 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Community Support Programs (CSP) Prize winners [RESTRICTED], 1994 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Community Support Programs (CSP) Task force brochure, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Community Support Programs (CSP)- Office of Mental Health, 1979; 1991 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Community Support Programs (CSP)-Report on future of CSPs in New York State, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 2-3)
  - Community Support Programs (CSP) Grant with Office of Mental Health, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 4-5)
  - Community Support Programs (CSP) Grant with Office of Mental Health- Audit, 1990; 1993; 1995 (Box 3, Folder 6-7)
  - Community Support Programs (CSP) task force matrix, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Comprehensive Housing Affordability Strategy-CHAS, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 9-10)
  - Comprehensive Housing Affordability Strategy (CHAS) and Division of Housing and Community Renewal (DHCR), 1996 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Conference Committee listing/representation, 1997-2001 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Developmental Disabilities Committee, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Developmental Disabilities Committee: Elimination of OMRDD waitlist/NY Cares, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Developmental Disabilities Committee: Meeting minutes, 1994 October (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Developmental Disabilities Committee: Meeting minutes, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Developmental Disabilities Committee: Meeting minutes, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Developmental Disabilities Committee: New member correspondence, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Developmental Disabilities Committee: Pilot Programs and Partnership Committee, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Developmental Disabilities Committee: Service Coordination Network software, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Developmental Disabilities Committee: "Supporting People with Developmental Disabilities and Their Families" OMRDD guide, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Development Disabilities Committee: Survey materials, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Developmental disabilities matrix, 1993; 1995; 1997 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Disabilities newsletters: Highlights from NYS Assembly and Task Force, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Executive Committee-Fall Membership Meeting, 1996 October (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Executive Committee Matrix, Undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1997 January (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Full conference matrix, Undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Governor's Office on Information Resource Management-Human Services Workgroup, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Homeless and Mentally ill veterans workgroup, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Housing Task Force of the M.H.S.C., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - I.S.O. steering committee, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Kids Oneida: Annual Report, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Kids Oneida: Background packet, wraparound care, 1992; 1997; 1999 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Kids Oneida: Briefing information and background materials, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Kids Oneida: Building a plan of care (POC), Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Kids Oneida: Chapter 433 of laws of 1997- Kids Oneida not a special needs plan, Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Kids Oneida: Children's mental healthcare models, New York and Oregon, 1990-1995 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Kids Oneida: Children's system of care/Wraparound service, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Kids Oneida: "Conducting High Performance Kids Oneida Child and Family Team Meetings", 1996 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Kids Oneida: Contact list and ICAN flow charts, Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Kids Oneida: Covered services, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Kids Oneida: "Crosswalk" between Kids Oneida service codes and NYS Medicaid-State plan services rate codes, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Kids Oneida: Evaluation methodology, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Kids Oneida: "Family Matters" newsletters, 1991 Fall; 2002 Spring (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Kids Oneida: Final report on integrated delivery systems, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Kids Oneida: Funding/payment policies, 1998; 2000 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Kids Oneida: Innovation Board, 1991-1994; 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Kids Oneida: Innovation Board, 1992-1994 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Kids Oneida: "Lessons Learned-Challenges, Obstacles, and Creative Solutions", 1998 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Kids Oneida: "Managed Care and Children's Mental Health-Summary of May 1995 State Managed Care Meeting", 1996 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Kids Oneida: Managed care and children's welfare, 1994; 1996 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Kids Oneida: "A Plan for Children, Youth and Family-Mental Health Services in Oneida County", 1985 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Kids Oneida: Planning and implementation, 1994; 1997-1998; Undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Kids Oneida: Planning and implementation, 1993-1998 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Kids Oneida: Planning and implementation, 1991; 1997-1998; Undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Kids Oneida: Planning and implementation, 1996-1998 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Kids Oneida: Policy recommendations, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Kids Oneida: Quality Assurance Outcome Measures, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Kids Oneida: Regulations, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Kids Oneida: Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, Indiana workgroup, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Kids Oneida: Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, Interagency Memorandum of Understanding, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Kids Oneida: Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, legislation model, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Kids Oneida: Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, stark county, Ohio program, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Kids Oneida: Steering committee materials, 1995-1997 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Kids Oneida: Tier III workgroup, 1997; 2000 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Kids Oneida: Ventura Planning Model, 1987; 1990 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Kids Oneida: Welcome Packet, Undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Local government issues subcommittee, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Mandate Relief Workgroup, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Mental Health Action Network steering committee, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Mental Health Committee, 1993-1997 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Mental Health Committee Meeting, 1997 September (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Mental Health matrix, Undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Missouri Institute of Mental Health, Spring Meeting, St. Louis, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - New York Community Trust Grant Proposal, 1990-1993 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - New York Community Trust Proposal, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - New York Community Trust Proposal, 1980; 1989; 1992 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - New York Community Trust File, 1991-1993 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - New York Community Trust File, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Nominating committees for 1994 and 1996, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - NYSAC- Welfare, Medicaid, children and families standing committee, 1997-1998; 2004 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Office of Mental Health: Children's Mental Health Advisory Group, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Office of Mental Health-Planning steering committee, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Office of Mental Health-Planning steering committee, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Office of Mental Retardation and Developmental Disabilities/Conference of Local Mental Hygiene Directors Partnership Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Office of Mental Retardation and Developmental Disabilities/Conference of Local Mental Hygiene Directors Partnership Committee, 1994-1997 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Partnership Committee: Pilot subcommittee members, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Partnership Committee: Pilot subcommittee, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Policy Resource Center, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Rural steering committee, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Rural steering committee, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Rural steering committee: Rural Outpatient Project, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Rural steering committee: Rural Outpatient Project Background, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Rural steering committee: Rural Outpatient Project Notes, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 27-28)
  - Rural steering committee: Rural Outpatient Project Report- Drafts, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Rural steering committee: Rural Outpatient Project Report-Drafts and Final, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Rural steering committee: Rural Outpatient Project, Team One, 1993-1995 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Single state agencies for mental health, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Managed Care and Special Needs Plans, 1991-2000; Undated; 6; 2.0 cu. ft.